

BLOCKCHAIN DEVELOPER

## **Details**

9558580469

mohammedlokhand4429@gmail.com

NATIONALITY

Indian

DATE / PLACE OF BIRTH

16/11/2000

Ahmedabad

#### Links

**Twitter** 

LinkedIn

**JavaScript** 

NodeJS

Skills
Blockchain
React js
Solidity
HTML
Web3.js
Truffle
CSS
Bootstrap

# **Profile**

Hi, I'm Mohammed, a skilled **Web and Blockchain develope**r with 1.5 years experience in **React**, **Angular**, **and smart contract** development. I've contributed to web3 open source projects and am open to all project types. I value clear communication and strive for success through collaboration. Let's create something great together!

# **Employment History**

Blockchain Developer, at Sunflowee Biztech, Ahmedabad

SEPTEMBER 2022 - PRESENT

Angular Developer, at Arishti Info Labs, Ahmedabad

AUGUST 2021 - AUGUST 2022

# Education

B.Tech in Computer Science and Engineering , Indrashil University, Rajpur

# **Project**

#### **UNITE3**, Contribution Power as NFT

- Develop platform using React js for viewing, claiming, and contributing to UNITE3 projects as NFTs.
- Create secure smart contracts in Solidity for NFT transactions and ownership.
- Integrate smart contracts with React js for transparent management of contributions on UNITE3.
- Check out my GitHub Repo: <a href="https://github.com/Mohammed-16/UNITE3">https://github.com/Mohammed-16/UNITE3</a>

# Open Bazzar, NFT marketplace

- Develop NFT marketplace using React js for user-friendly interface.
- Build secure smart contracts in Solidity for NFT transactions.
- Integrate smart contracts with React js for easy NFT trading on Open Bazzar.
- Check out my GitHub Repo: https://github.com/Mohammed-16/OpenBazaar

## Yield Farming, Blockchain

- Developed a DeFi app using Solidity, Web3, Truffle, and React js.
- Optimized usability and implemented Back-end for ERC-20 Token.
- Check out my GitHub Repo: https://github.com/Mohammed-16/Yield-Farming-DeFi-ERC20-Token-

#### **Courses**

Blockchain, Ethereum & Solidity, Udemy

JUNE 2022 - AUGUST 2022

## React js, Udemy

JANUARY 2021 - MARCH 2021

# **College Grade**

Sem VIII, 10.00 SGPA

Overall, 8.63 CGPA